pricedekho.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy Policy | PriceDekho.com

Girnar Software Private Limited and its affiliates, subsidiaries & associate companies as mentioned in this Privacy Policy (hereinafter referred individually and/ or collectively as " **Girnar** ") is/are concerned about the privacy of the data and information of the users accessing, offering, selling or purchasing products or services on **Girnar** websites, mobile sites or mobile applications or otherwise doing business with **Girnar**. This Privacy Policy help you understand how we collect, use, store, process, transfer and protect all your information when you visit any of our Website (defined below) and use our products and services. 

THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS AN ELECTRONIC RECORD IN THE FORM OF ELECTRONIC CONTRACT IN TERMS OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 2000 AND RULES MADE THEREUNDER (AS AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME) AND DOES NOT REQUIRE ANY PHYSICAL SIGNATURE OR SEAL. 

This Privacy Policy is applicable to www.pricedekho.com, “PriceDekho” application for mobile and handheld devices (the “App”) and “PriceDekho” chrome extension (the “Chrome Extension”, a PriceDekho extension for the Google Chrome browser).

The term “We”/ “Us” / “Our” used in this document refer to **Girnar** and "You" / "Your" / "Yourself" refer to the users, who visit or access or use or avail any service or product (collectively “usage”) on or through Site/App/Chrome Extension (individually and collectively, “Website”).

## TERMS AND CONDITIONS: 

**Acknowledgment:**   
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. YOU INDICATE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND, AGREE AND CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. HENCE BY VISITING OUR WEBSITE OR BY USING / AVAILING ANY OF OUR SERVICE OR PRODUCT, YOU HEREBY GIVE YOUR UNCONDITIONAL CONSENT OR AGREEMENTS TO GIRNAR AS PROVIDED UNDER SECTION 43A AND SECTION 72A OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 2000 FOR COLLECTION, USE, STORAGE, PROCESSING AND TRANSFER AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION. 

YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE ALL LEGAL RIGHTS AND LAWFUL AUTHORITY TO SHARE THE INFORMATION WITH US AND FURTHER ACKNOWLEDGE THAT BY COLLECTING, SHARING, PROCESSING AND TRANSFERRING INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU, THIS SHALL NOT CAUSE ANY LOSS OR WRONGFUL GAIN TO YOU OR ANY OTHER PERSON. 

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS / USE OUR WEBSITE OR AVAIL ANY OF OUR SERVICE OR PRODUCT ON OUR WEBSITE. 

## Topics Covered: 

This policy is designed to make you understand: 

  * The type of information which You share with Us or which We collect during Your usage to Website.
  * The purpose of such collection, storage, processing and transferring of Your Information.
  * Security measures implemented by Us to protect Your Information as mandated by law.
  * Disclosure, sharing and transfer of Your personal information.

## Information We Collect (Your Information) and store: 

We collect Your information during your usage to Website or when you avail any of services or products available on or through Our Website, either as a registered user or otherwise. The information collected may consists of: 

  * Your Personal Information including Your name, age, address, email id, phone number, date of birth, gender, financial information, any other sensitive personal data or information etc. 
  * Non-personal information which may include your geographical location, IP address, your system details like OS version, internet browser & your telecom service provider etc. 

We may receive Your Information from third parties such as social media, and in such case, the information We collect may include your user name associated with that social media, any information or content the social media has the right to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends list, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media. When you access the Website or otherwise deal with any **Girnar** entity through social media, you are authorizing **Girnar** to collect, store, use and retain such information and content in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

Information may be collected through various ways such through the use of cookies. **Girnar** may store temporary or permanent "cookies" on Your computer. "Cookies" are files situated on Your mobile/ computer/device's hard disk that assist Us in providing customised services. A cookie helps Us analyse Your preferences, for example, recording the number of times You have used the Website, and help us in tailoring Our services to suit Your interests. Further, there are certain features of the Website that are available only through the use of a "cookie". These "cookies" may be used whether You register on the Website or not. You can erase or choose to block these cookies from Your computer. You can configure Your computer’s browser to alert You when we attempt to send You a cookie with an option to accept or refuse the cookie. If You have turned cookies off, You may be prevented from using certain features of the Website. Further, we may use third-party service providers to serve ads on **Girnar** behalf across the internet and sometimes on the Website. They may collect Non- personal information about Your visits to the Website, and Your interaction with the products and services on the Website.

Your Information will mostly be stored in electronic form however certain data may be stored in physical form. We may store, collect, use and process Your Information in countries other than Republic of India subject to compliance under applicable laws. We may enter into agreements with third parties (in or outside of India) to store or process Your Information and such third parties may have their own security measures to safeguard Your Information.

**Browser Add-on** : Add-on or Extensions are software programs that can modify and/or enhance the functionality of browsers. You can add PriceDekho Extensions to your browser (Chrome, Firefox etc.) for a more personalised experience like better price comparison, trending products, price drop alerts, exclusive coupons, etc. Add-on / Extension can access your data on all the websites you visit, the tabs and the browsing activity of the browser. Add-on / Extension is stored locally to provide a better user experience for You. We would capture Your email address so as to notify You with relevant information. We would also capture other details to provide You a better user experience. 

When You add PriceDekho to Google Chrome as Chrome Extension, You explicitly permit Us as well as third parties, to the extent apply, to display notifications, read and change Your browsing history, read and change Your bookmarks, manage Your apps, extensions and themes, detect Your physical locations, read all Your data on the website and other changes.

##  Purpose of Collection, Storage, Processing: 

**Girnar** collect Your Information solely for the purpose of providing you the product or service that is connected with the function or activity of the **Girnar** which includes but not limited to the following (“Purpose”): 

  * To inform You about various products and services offered on Our Website. 
  * To address Your queries and resolve your concerns pertaining to any service or product that you were looking for. 
  * To send you survey and marketing communications or facilitate various programmes and initiatives launched either by Us or third party which We believes may be of interest to You.
  * To facilitate Your usage of Website and improve Our Service, product or content on Website.
  * To review Website performance and do data analysis to make Your experience better.
  * To protect the integrity of Our Website.
  * To inform You about change in any term and condition of this Privacy Policy or Terms of Use of any Website of **Girnar**.
  * To implement information security practices, to determine any security breaches, contaminant or computer virus, to investigate/prevent/take action illegal activities and suspected fraud.

You permit us to collect Chrome Extension usage statistics to help improve user experience and if You want to opt-out of Google Analytics tracking, the same can be done by visiting http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout or user can set up a filter in Adblock Plus or similar ad blocker tools like AdBlock, uBlock or Adblock Pro. 

## Sharing, Transfer or Disclosure: 

Any service or product provided through Our Website may be provided either by **Girnar** or its vendor, dealer, OEM, channel partners and other third parties (“other entities”) which are registered with **Girnar** to render the services or provide products through Website. 

You acknowledge and agree that **Girnar** may share, disclose, transfer or part with Your Information to other entities depending upon the type of service or product You are looking for or for one or more of the permissible purposes. **Girnar** may also share Your personal or non-personal information where it is required to share the same with such other entities for providing you the service or product and You provide **Girnar** , Your unconditional consent to do the same.

**Girnar** may share statistical data and/or other Non-personal Information or details without your express or implied consent to facilitate various program or initiatives launched by **Girnar** , third party service providers, partners or financial institutions, from time to time.

We use other third parties such as a credit/debit card processing company, payment gateway, pre-paid cards etc. to enable You to make payments for buying products or availing services on Website. When You sign up for these services, You may have the ability to save Your card details for future reference and faster future payments. In such case, We may share Your relevant Information as necessary for the third parties to provide such services, including your name, residence and email address. The processing of payments or authorization is solely in accordance with these third parties policies, terms and conditions and we are not in any manner responsible or liable to You or any third party for any delay or failure at their end in processing the payments.

In addition to this, **Girnar** reserve the right to share Your Information with any Government Agency or other authorized law enforcement agencies (LEAs) mandated under law to obtain Your Information for the purpose of verification of identity or for prevention, detection, investigation including but not limited to cyber incidents, prosecution, and punishment of offences etc.

## Third Party Links: 

It is clarified that while Your usage to Our Website, you might see the links to the third party website / advertisements / electronic communication service, which are provided by the third parties. As the operation of the third party is not under control **Girnar** , therefore **Girnar** does not make any endorsement / guarantee of any service or product offered through third party websites nor make any representation related to the any privacy policy or other policies of such third party. Any usage of such third party website or availing any service or product through third party shall be at Your risk and **Girnar** is not responsible for any loss / damage or otherwise. 

It is recommended that You should review the privacy policy of such third party websites prior to using such websites.

## Security Measures: 

**Girnar** takes utmost care to secure Your Information from unauthorised access, usage or disclosure or alteration. We take appropriate steps and security measures to safeguard Your Information and make sure that Your Information is secured as mandated by law. For this purpose we adopt reasonable security practices and procedures, in line with the industry standard, to include, technical, operational, managerial and physical security controls in order to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, or disclosure while it is under our control. 

While We protect Your Personal information as per industry standards, You acknowledge that the internet or computer networks are not fully secure and that We cannot provide any absolute assurance regarding the security of Your Personal information. Therefore You acknowledge that You shall not hold responsible **Girnar** in any manner whatsoever for loss of Your Information, or any other data, which You shares with Us or which We have with Us if such loss or any damage caused to You because of Force Majeure events. You further acknowledge that any information (including your personal information) transmitted to Us or from Your use of Website will therefore be at Your own risk.

It is clarified that Force Majeure events includes any event which is beyond the reasonable control of the **Girnar** which may include but not limited to sabotage, fire, flood, explosion, acts of God, civil commotion, strikes or industrial action of any kind, riots, insurrection, war, acts of government, computer hacking, unauthorised access to computer, computer system or computer network, computer crashes, breach of security and encryption.

## Update of Your Information: 

**Girnar** take all endeavours to update Our records with latest information as provided by you, however if you see any discrepancy in your personal information you may contact to Us through Grievance Officer to have Your Information updated with Us. 

You also acknowledge that all the information provided by You are out of Your free will and in compliance with applicable laws in Your territory. If We found that any of Your Information is in non-compliance with the terms and conditions and Privacy policy, **Girnar** reserves the right to remove your non-compliant information from its systems. Further, depending on the seriousness of the non-compliance, We may choose to discontinue some or all of the services being provided to You by Us.

## Authorization: 

In purview of the Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI) guidelines, You hereby authorize **Girnar** and its affiliates/partners or otherwise who are accessing the Your Information by virtue of their association with **Girnar** to communicate with You through telephone/mobile, Email, SMS or other modes of communication even if Yours number/numbers(s) is/are registered in the National Do Not Call Registry (NDNC) or www.nccptrai.gov.in 

## Change in terms of Privacy Policy: 

**Girnar** reserves the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time, as and when the need arises. We request you to regularly check this Privacy Policy from time to time to keep you apprise of changes made. Your continued use of the Website gives your unconditional acceptance to such change in terms of Privacy Policy. 

**Particulars of corporate entity, Grievance Officer pursuant to the provisions of Companies Act, 2013 and The Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules made thereunder:**

The particulars of various corporate entities of Girnar for the above purposes are as under: 

  * Girnar Software Private Limited   
CIN: U72200RJ2006PTC023499  
Registered office address: Girnar 21, Govind Marg, Moti Doongari Road, Dharm Singh Circle, Jaipur, Rajasthan- 302004, India
  * Gaadi Web Private Limited  
CIN: U72300DL2007PTC169207  
Registered office address: F-130, GF, Street No.7, Pandav Nagar Delhi - 110091, India
  * Girnarsoft Education Services Private Limited  
CIN: U80302RJ2015PTC047265  
Registered office address: Girnar 21, Govind Marg, Moti Doongari Road, Dharm Singh Circle, Jaipur, Rajasthan- 302004, India
  * Girnarsoft Automobiles Private Limited  
CIN: U50300RJ2010PTC032194  
Registered office address: Girnar 21, Govind Marg, Moti Doongari Road, Dharm Singh Circle, Jaipur, Rajasthan- 302004, India

If you have any concern related to this Privacy Policy or collection, storage, retention or disclosure of Your Information under the terms of this Privacy Policy or Terms of Use or any other terms and conditions of Girnar or its other business entities including any queries or grievances, You can contact to Girnar through its Grievance Redressal Officer at the below given details: 

Name | :  | Mr. Sunny Bajaj  
---|---|---  
E-mail  | :  | legal@girnarsoft.com  
Telephone Number | :  | 0124-6510130  
Working Days | :  | Monday to Friday  
Working Hours | :  | 10:30 am to 6:30 pm  
  
We will strive to address your feedback and concerns in a timely and effective manner. 

Please note that the details of the grievance officer may be changed by Us from time to time by updating this Privacy Policy.
